(Sheldon:)I'm sure he didn't care about
silly superstitions like funerals.
(Sheldon:)You know, if he were here,
(Sheldon:)I think he'd say,
"Enjoy Star Wars Day."
(Leonard:)He was 84.
He'd say, "Where's my pudding?"
(Raj:)Before you go, at least
let me pack you some
(Raj:)Attack of the Scones
for the road.
(Penny:)Oh, like Attack of the Clones.
We are leaving right now!
(Amy:)Arthur passing away
was harder on Sheldon
(Amy:)than he's ready to admit.
(Amy:)Really hoping this will cheer him up.
(Bernadette:)Me, too.
(Bernadette:)Although, it might've been
thoughtless of us
(Bernadette:)to bake a Death Star cake.
(Amy:)No, it combines two of
(Amy:)chocolate chips and the ability
to destroy a planet
(Amy:)at the push of a button.
(Bernadette:)Well, anyway, it'll be
a nice surprise for the boys.
(Bernadette:)And Howie doesn't think
I take his interests seriously,
(Bernadette:)so hopefully this will keep
him fooled for a while.
OK, let's get the fondant
and start decorating.
(Bernadette:)This is pretty cool.
(Bernadette:)You don't see too many
spherical cakes.